Finding aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) records, 1900-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library
- Press Release File, 1945-2008
  - 1945-1956 (Box 12)
    - Business and Finance
      - Financial Report (Box 13)
    - Communist Investigations (Box 13)
    - Conferences
      - Miscellaneous, 1950-1952 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous No. 2 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 13)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1952 (Box 14)
      - Arab Conference, 1952 (Box 14)
      - Blind Conference, 1947 (Box 14)
      - Canada-U.S. Committee on Education, 1952 (Box 14)
      - Citizenship Conference, 1951 (Box 14)
      - Community Health Services, Michigan Conference on, 1949 (Box 14)
      - Guidance Conference, 1947 (Box 14)
      - Higher Education, Conference on, 1947 (Box 14)
      - Higher Education, Conference on, 1955-1956 (Box 14)
      - Michigan Academy of Science, Arts and Letters, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Michigan Interscholastic Press Association (Box 14)
      - Michigan Schoolmasters Club, 8 folders (Box 14)
      - Pastors' Conference (Box 14)
      - Preventative Medicine, Conference on, 1946 (Box 14)
      - Rural Health Conference, 1952 (Box 14)
      - TB Conference, 1952 (Box 14)
      - Tax Assessors Conference (Box 14)
      - University Press Club, 5 folders (Box 14)
      - Wolverine Girls' State (Box 14)
    - Dentistry (Box 14)
    - Drama Season (Box 14)
    - Education, School of, 5 folders (Box 15)
    - Engineering, College of, 3 folders
      - Engineering Centennial (Box 15)
      - Transportation Institute
        - Railroad Management Seminar (Box 15)
      - International Congress on Nuclear Engineering (Box 15)
    - Engineering Research Institute, 2 folders
      - Willow Run Research Center (Box 15)
    - English Language Institute (Box 16)
    - Extension Service, 6 folders
      - Adult Education (Box 16)
      - Institute Coal Utilization Institute (Box 16)
      - Fire College (Box 16)
      - Real Estate Clinic (Box 16)
    - Faculty, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 16)
    - Governing Board, Association of (Box 16)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of
      - Fulbright Awards (Box 16)
    - Great Lakes Research Institute Haven Hall Fire (Box 16)
    - Health Service (Box 16)
    - Hospital (University)
      - 1946-1952 (Box 16)
      - 1954-1956 (Box 17)
      - Children's Hospital (Box 17)
      - Kresge Medical Research (Box 17)
      - Pharmacy (Hospital) (Box 17)
      - Outpatient Clinic (Box 17)
      - Respirator Clinic (Box 17)
      - Women's Hospital (Box 17)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Human Adjustment
      - Aging Conference (Box 17)
    - Human Biology (Box 17)
    - International Center, 2 folders
      - Foreign Students (Box 17)
    - Intra-University Services
      - Plant Department (Box 17)
    - Japanese Studies (Box 17)
    - Law School
      - Cooley Lectures (Box 17)
      - Law School Summer Institute (Box 17)
      - William W. Cook Lectures (Box 18)
    - Lectures, 2 folders
      - Henry Russel Lectures (Box 18)
      - Mott Foundation Lectures (Box 18)
      - University Lectures Committee (Box 18)
    - Legislature (Box 18)
    - Libraries
      - Clement Library (Box 18)
      - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 18)
      - Stellfield Collections (Box 18)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Anthropology (Box 18)
      - Astronomy, 3 folders
        - McMath Hulbert Observatory (Box 18)
        - Observatory (Box 18)
      - Botany (Box 18)
      - Chemistry (Box 18)
      - Classical Studies (Box 19)
      - Economics (Box 19)
      - English
        - Hopwood Awards, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Far Eastern Studies (Box 19)
      - Fine Arts (Box 19)
      - Geography (Box 19)
      - Geology (Box 19)
      - History
        - Jerome Lectures (Box 19)
      - Journalism, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Languages (Box 19)
      - Library Science (Box 19)
      - Mathematics (Box 19)
      - Mineralogy (Box 19)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 19)
      - Philosophy (Box 19)
      - Physical Education (Box 19)
      - Physics (Box 19)
      - Political Science (Box 19)
      - Psychology (Box 19)
      - Sociology (Box 19)
      - Speech, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Zoology (Box 20)
    - Medical School
      - General, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Industrial Health (Box 20)
    - Military Activities
      - ROTC, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Veterans' Readjustment Center, 5 folders (Box 20)
    - Museums
      - Archaeology (Box 20)
      - Art, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Exhibits (Box 21)
    - Music, School of
      - General, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Interlochen (Box 21)
      - Stanley Quartet (Box 21)
      - Woodwind Quintet (Box 21)
    - Musical Activities
      - Bands, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Band Day (Box 21)
      - Carillon (Box 21)
      - Choirs (Box 21)
      - Concert Band (Box 21)
      - Glee Club (Box 21)
      - Little Symphony (Box 21)
      - Marching Band (Box 21)
      - Michigan Singers (Box 22)
      - Symphony Band (Box 22)
      - Symphony Orchestra (Box 22)
    - Musical Society
      - Chamber Music Festival (Box 22)
      - Choral Union, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Concerts (Box 22)
      - May Festival (Box 22)
      - "Messiah" (Box 22)
    - Natural Resources, School of
      - Conservation Department (Box 22)
      - Fisheries Department (Box 22)
      - Forestry (Box 22)
      - Wildlife Management (Box 22)
      - Wood Technology (Box 22)
    - Naval Research (Box 22)
    - News Service (Box 22)
    - North Campus
      - Mortimer E. Cooley Building Nursing (Box 22)
    - Oratorical Association (Box 22)
    - Personnel Office
      - Employees (Box 22)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 23)
    - Phoenix Project
      - General, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Fission Products Laboratory (Box 23)
      - Progress Reports (Box 23)
    - Psychological Services (Box 23)
    - Public Administration
      - General, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Bureau of Government (Box 23)
    - Public Health, School of
      - General, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Research (Box 23)
      - Virology Laboratory (Box 23)
    - Radio: WUOM, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Regents, 7 folders (Box 24)
    - Registrar (Box 24)
    - Registrar
      - Enrollment, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Freshmen, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Grades (Box 25)
      - Principal-Freshman Conference, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Research
      - General, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Midwestern Universities Research Council (Box 25)
      - Polio Vaccine Evaluation (Box 25)
    - Sanitation Foundation (National) (Box 25)
    - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 25)
    - School Services, Bureau of, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Social Research Institute
      - Group Dynamics (Box 25)
      - Survey Research Center, 4 folders
        - Detroit Area Study, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 26)
    - Speech Clinic, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Statistical Research Lab (Box 26)
    - Student Activities
      - General, 3 folders (Box 26)
      - Fraternities and Sororities, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Joint Judiciary Council (Box 26)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 26)
      - Michigan League (Box 26)
      - Michigan Union (Box 26)
      - Student Legislature (Box 26)
      - Student Productions (Box 26)
      - Student Religious Association (Box 26)
      - University Day (Box 26)
    - Student Affairs (Office of) (Box 26)
    - Student Honors
      - Honor Awards (Box 26)
    - Summer Session
      - General, 3 folders (Box 26)
      - Summer Camps
        - Fresh Air Camp (Box 26)
      - Summer Lectures, 7 folders (Box 27)
    - Television, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - University Administration
      - Development Council (Box 27)
    - University of Michigan (General)
      - Awards to University (Box 27)
      - Detroit Plaque Dedication (Box 27)
      - Events (Box 27)
      - Hatcher Inauguration (Box 27)
      - History of and Seal (Box 27)
      - Miscellaneous Information on U of M (Box 27)
      - Presidents (Box 27)
    - University Press (Box 27)
    - University Relations
      - Ann Arbor, City of (Box 27)
      - College Relations Committee (Box 27)
    - University Press (Box 28)
      - Other Colleges and Universities
        - Michigan State College, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Investigations
        - McPhaul Investigation (Box 28)
    - Vision Research Laboratory (Box 28)
    - Visitors, 2 folders
      - Queen Juliana's Visit (Box 28)
    - Willow Run Airport
      - General, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Dedication (Box 28)
  - 1957-1958
    - Admissions (Box 28)
    - Alumni, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Appointments, Bureau of, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 28)
    - Art (Box 28)
    - Athletics (Box 28)
    - Audio-Visual Education Center (Box 28)
    - Broadcasting
      - Radio-WUOM (Box 28)
      - Television (Box 28)
    - Buildings (Box 29)
    - Business Administration, School of, 2 folders
      - Conferences (Box 29)
      - Industrial Relations (Box 29)
      - Business Research, Bureau of (Box 29)
      - Hospital Administration Program (Box 29)
    - Business and Finance
      - Appropriations-Capital Outlay (Box 29)
      - Appropriations-General Fund (Box 29)
      - Budget (Box 29)
      - Fees (Box 29)
      - Parking (Box 29)
    - Conferences
      - Michigan Schoolmasters' Club (Box 29)
      - University Press Club (Box 29)
      - Wolverine Girls' State (Box 29)
    - Curriculum, General (Box 29)
    - Dearborn Center (Box 29)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 29)
    - Development Council (Box 29)
    - Education, School of, 2 folders
      - Education Conferences (Box 29)
      - University School (Box 29)
    - Engineering, College of, 2 folders
      - Engineering Conferences (Box 29)
      - Aeronautical Engineering (Box 29)
      - Automotive Engineering Laboratory (Box 29)
      - Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering (Box 29)
      - Civil Engineering (Box 29)
      - Electrical Engineering (Box 29)
      - Engineering Drawing (Box 29)
      - Engineering English (Box 29)
      - Engineering Mechanics (Box 29)
      - Engineering Research (Box 29)
      - Fluids Engineering Laboratory (Box 29)
      - Industrial Engineering (Box 29)
      - Marine Engineering (Box 29)
      - Mechanical Engineering (Box 29)
      - Meteorological Laboratory (Box 29)
      - Nuclear Engineering (Box 29)
      - Transportation Institute (Box 29)
    - Extension Service (Box 30)
      - Conferences (Box 30)
      - Adult Education, Division of (Box 30)
    - Faculty
      - General, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Faculty Honors, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Henry Russel Lectures (Box 30)
      - University Senate (Box 30)
    - Fisheries Research, Institute for (Box 30)
    - Flint College of the U of M (Box 30)
    - Foundations
      - Ford Foundation (Box 30)
      - National Sanitation Foundation (Box 30)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 30)
      - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 30)
    - Gerontology, Division of
      - Aging Conference (Box 30)
      - Legislative Advisory Council (Box 30)
    - Graduate Studies (Box 30)
    - Great Lakes Commission
      - Great Lakes Fisheries Commission (Box 30)
      - Great Lakes Research Institute (Box 30)
    - Health Service (Box 30)
    - Honors Council (Box 30)
    - Hospital-University, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute for
      - Fresh Air Camp (Box 30)
      - Psychological Services, Bureau of (Box 30)
      - Social Science Research Project (Box 30)
      - Speech Clinic (Box 30)
    - Human Resources (Box 30)
    - International Center (Box 31)
    - Intra-University Services
      - Plant Department (Box 31)
    - Japanese Studies (Box 31)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Law School, 2 folders
      - Institutes and conferences (Box 31)
      - Michigan Law Review (Box 31)
      - Legislative Research Center (Box 31)
    - Lectures
      - Oratorical Association (Box 31)
      - Platform Attractions (Box 31)
      - University Lectures Committee (Box 31)
    - Legislature (Box 31)
    - Libraries
      - General Library (Box 31)
      - Clements Library (Box 31)
      - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 31)
      - Undergraduate Library (Box 31)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
      - Anthropology (Box 31)
      - Asian Studies (Box 31)
      - Astronomy (Box 31)
      - Botany (Box 31)
      - Chemistry (Box 31)
      - Classical Studies (Box 31)
      - Economics (Box 31)
      - English
        - Hopwood Awards (Box 31)
        - English Language Institute (Box 31)
      - Far Eastern Studies (Box 31)
      - Fine Arts (Box 31)
      - Geography (Box 31)
      - Geology (Box 31)
      - German (Box 31)
      - History (Box 31)
      - Journalism, 2 folders
        - Michigan Journalist (Box 31)
      - Latin American Studies (Box 32)
      - Library Science (Box 32)
      - Mammalian Genetics Center (Box 32)
      - Mathematics
        - Statistical Research Lab (Box 32)
      - Mineralogy (Box 32)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 32)
      - Philosophy (Box 32)
      - Physical Education (Box 32)
      - Physics (Box 32)
      - Political Science (Box 32)
      - Psychology
        - Vision Research Laboratory (Box 32)
      - Religion, Committee on Studies in (Box 32)
      - Romance Languages (Box 32)
      - Russian Studies Slavic Languages (Box 32)
      - Sociology (Box 32)
      - Speech
        - Speech Plays (Box 32)
      - Zoology (Box 32)
    - Medical School
      - General, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Medical Research (Box 32)
      - Medical School Conferences (Box 32)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 32)
    - Military Science and Tactics (Box 32)
    - Museums
      - Exhibits (Box 32)
      - Herbarium (Box 32)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 32)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 32)
      - Museum of Art (Box 32)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 32)
    - Music, School of
      - General, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Interlochen (Box 32)
      - Stanley Quartet (Box 32)
    - Musical Activities
      - Bands (Box 32)
      - Choirs (Box 32)
      - Glee Club (Box 32)
      - Marching Band (Box 32)
      - Michigan Singers (Box 32)
      - Symphony Orchestra (Box 32)
    - Musical Society
      - Chamber Music Festival (Box 32)
      - Choral Union (Box 32)
      - May Festival (Box 32)
      - Messiah and other Concerts (Box 32)
    - Natural Resources, School of
      - Conservation (Box 32)
      - Fisheries (Box 32)
      - Forestry (Box 32)
      - Wildlife Management (Box 32)
      - Wood Technology (Box 32)
    - News Service (Box 33)
    - North Campus (Box 33)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 33)
    - Personnel Office (Box 33)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 33)
    - Phoenix Project
      - Ford Nuclear Reactor (Box 33)
      - Radiocarbon Dating Laboratory (Box 33)
    - Public Administration, Institute of (Box 33)
    - Public Health, School of, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Regents, Board of, 2 folders
      - Chronological File, 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Gifts and Grants, 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Citations of Honor (Box 33)
    - Registration and Records, Office of
      - Enrollment, 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Grades (Box 33)
    - Religious Affairs, Office of (Box 33)
    - Research
      - Daylighting Laboratory (Box 33)
      - Project Michigan (Box 33)
      - Bendix (Box 33)
      - Parke, Davis (Box 33)
      - Midwestern Universities Research Association (Box 33)
      - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 33)
      - Engineering Research Institute (Box 33)
      - Science Advisory Committee (Box 33)
    - School Services, Bureau of (Box 34)
      - Michigan Forensic Association (Box 34)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 34)
    - Statewide Education (Box 34)
    - Student Activities
      - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 34)
      - Joint Judiciary Council (Box 34)
      - Michigan League (Box 34)
      - Michigan Union (Box 34)
      - Social Events (Box 34)
      - Student Feature Stories (Box 34)
      - Student Government Council (Box 34)
    - Student Aid
      - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowships (Box 34)
    - Student Affairs, Office of
      - Dean of Men (Box 34)
      - Dean of Women (Box 34)
      - Student Honors, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Summer Session
      - Summer Camps (Box 34)
    - Survey Research Center, 2 folders
      - Social Research Institute (Box 34)
      - Group Dynamics (Box 34)
      - Detroit Area Study (Box 34)
    - University Administration
      - Et Cetera (Box 34)
      - President's office (Box 34)
    - University of Michigan (General)
      - Events (Box 34)
      - History of and Seal (Box 34)
      - Miscellaneous Information (Box 34)
    - University Press (Box 34)
    - University Relations (Box 35)
      - American College Public Relations Association, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Ann Arbor, City of (Box 35)
      - Investigations (Box 35)
      - Other Colleges and Universities
        - Wayne State University (Box 35)
    - Visitors (Box 35)
    - Willow Run Airport (Box 35)
    - Willow Run Laboratories (Box 35)
  - 1959-1960
    - Dearborn Center (Box 35)
    - Medical Center (Box 35)
    - Student Government Council (Box 35)
  - 1963 (Box 50)
    - February (Box 50)
    - March (Box 50)
    - April (Box 50)
    - September (Box 50)
    - October, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - December (Box 50)
  - 1964
    - February (Box 50)
    - March (Box 50)
    - May (Box 50)
    - June (Box 50)
    - July (Box 50)
    - August (Box 50)
    - September (Box 51)
    - October (Box 51)
    - November (Box 51)
    - December (Box 51)
  - 1965
    - January (Box 51)
    - February (Box 51)
    - March (Box 51)
    - April (Box 51)
    - May (Box 51)
    - August (Box 51)
    - September (Box 51)
    - October (Box 51)
    - November (Box 52)
    - December (Box 52)
  - 1966
    - January (Box 52)
    - February (Box 52)
    - March (Box 52)
    - April (Box 52)
    - May (Box 52)
    - June (Box 52)
    - July (Box 52)
    - August (Box 52)
    - September (Box 52)
    - October (Box 53)
    - November (Box 53)
    - December (Box 53)
  - 1967
    - January (Box 53)
    - February (Box 53)
    - March (Box 53)
    - April (Box 53)
    - May (Box 53)
    - June (Box 53)
    - July (Box 53)
    - August (Box 53)
    - September (Box 53)
    - November (Box 53)
  - 1962-2008
    - 1962-67, 1968-71 (scattered dates) (Box 77)
    - October 1980-December 1983 (Box 77)
    - January 1984-December 1988 (Box 78)
    - January 1989-July 1993 (Box 120)
    - January 1994-December 1998 (Box 150)
    - January 1999-February 2000 (Box 167)
    - June 2000-December 2001 (Box 167)
    - January 2002-March 2005 (Box 168)
    - August 2005-December 2005 (Box 168)
    - January 2006-March 2008 (Box 169)
    - September 2008-October 2008 (Box 169)
- Faculty and Staff Files
  (Removed during reprocessing. See News and Information Service Faculty and Staff Files.)
- Gerald R. Ford, 1934-2000
  The GERALD R. FORD series (1 linear foot, 1934-2000) primarily consists of newspaper clippings, press releases, and other articles about Ford, which are arranged topically. The series documents Ford's career as congressman, Vice President, and President, and highlights other activities as well, including his service as adjunct professor at the University after his presidency, visits to the University, and the construction of the Gerald R. Ford Library. An outsize scrapbook from 1976 is housed separately. This scrapbook focuses on Gerald R. Ford's visit to the university.
  - Adjunct Professor, 1976-1980 (Box 170)
  - Biographical, 1973-1986 (Box 170)
  - Campaign Visit -- UM, 1976 (Box 170)
  - Commencement, 1974 (Box 170)
  - Congressman, 1949-1973 (Box 170)
  - Ford, Betty, 1973-1983 (Box 170)
  - Ford Endowment, 1987-1988 (Box 170)
  - Ford Presidential Library, 1974-1989 (Box 170)
  - Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - President of the United States, 1974-1977; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Press Clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 170)
  - Press Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 170)
  - Press Clippings, 1990-2000 (Box 170)
  - University of Michigan, 1934-1993 (Box 170)
  - Vice President, United States, 1973-1974 (Box 170)
  - Scrapbook primarily concerning President Ford's visit to U-M campus, 1976 (Volume 1)
    (located in BImu/C475)
- University Presidents, 1951-2001
  The UNIVERSITY PRESIDENTS series (4 linear feet, 1950-2001) documents the service of University Presidents Harlan H. Hatcher, Robben W. Fleming, Harold T. Shapiro, James J. Duderstadt, Lee C. Bollinger, and the interim service of Homer Neal. The records contain press releases and other news coverage concerning the University's presidents and their involvement both on campus and with national and world affairs. The series is arranged topically by president, with the exception being Duderstadt, whose records are arranged topically but also include a series of press clippings arranged chronologically by month and year, mirroring their original arrangement. The topics covered vary from president to president, although there are similar recurring themes for each president, including their selection and inauguration, their departure, biographical information, and speeches or issued by the president. Other general recurring topics include affirmative action and discrimination and the growth and funding of the University.
  - Hatcher, Harlan H.
    - Biographical Materials, 1955-1981 (Box 171)
    - Davis, Nickerson, and Merkert, 1989-1990 (Box 171)
    - Photographs, 1950-1995 (Box 171)
    - Power, Eugene -- Resignation, 1965-1966 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1951-1956 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1960-1963 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1964-1967 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1968-1995 (Box 171)
    - Soviet Union, 1959 (Box 171)
    - Speeches, 1957-1971 (Box 171)
    - Statements, 1952-1967 (Box 171)
  - Fleming, Robben W.
    - Agnew, Spiro, circa 1970 (Box 171)
    - Athletic Director Search, 1987-1988 (Box 171)
    - Biographical, 1968-1981 (Box 171)
    - Broadcasters Promotion Association, 1970-1989 (Box 171)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1979-1987 (Box 171)
    - Discrimination/Code of Conduct, 1987-1988 (Box 171)
    - Fleming, Sally, 1971-1988 (Box 171)
    - Inauguration, 1968 (Box 171)
    - Interim President, 1987-1988 (Box 171)
    - Malpractice Analysis, 1985-1990 (Box 171)
    - Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1972 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1973 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1974 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1975 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 171)
    - Press Clippings, 1980-1985 (Box 172)
    - Press Clippings, 1987-1996 (Box 172)
    - Protests, 1988 (Box 172)
    - Resignation, 1978-1979 (Box 172)
    - Steiner, Peter, 1988 (Box 172)
    - Speeches, 1967-1975 (Box 172)
    - Statements, 1968-1973 (Box 172)
  - Shapiro, Harold T.
    - Athletics, 1982-1987 (Box 172)
    - Biographical, 1965-1987 (Box 172)
    - Department Chairman, 1974 (Box 172)
    - Discrimination, 1980-1987 (Box 172)
    - Economy, 1969-1978 (Box 172)
    - Economy, 1979-1980 (Box 172)
    - Economy, 1981-1986 (Box 172)
    - Industry, Research and Scientific Collaboration, 1981-1989 (Box 172)
    - Photographs, 1980-1987; 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Press Clippings, 1977-1982 (Box 172)
    - Press Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 172)
    - Press Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 172)
    - Press Clippings, 1988-1998 (Box 172)